<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Book My Lube</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Book My Lube</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_book_service">BookServiceActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_us">About Us</string>
    <string name="title_activity_our_service">Our Service</string>
    <string name="title_activity_book_my_service">Service Booking</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact_us">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="title_activity_manage_booking">Manage Booking</string>
    <string name="aboutus">BookMyLube is Saskatoon\'s only one Doorstep Vehicle Service Business Quick, Convenient and professional - you\'ll never want to go back to the old brick and mortar method of getting your vehicle\'s Service Whether it\'s your personal vehicle, Business Vehicle or a whole fleet we do it all and we come to you, to do it! Simply Book your service through Application, Provide date, time and Location information and our Expert time will come to you to service your car.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin_booking">AdminBookingActivity</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="reload"><u>Reload page</u></string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms_conditions">Terms &amp; Conditions</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Gallery</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Slideshow</string>
    <string name="menu_tools">Tools</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_send">Send</string>

    <string name="TermsofUse">This App is owned by BookMyLube 11275135 Canada Inc. in its capacity as general partner of and for the partners of BookMyLube Canada Limited Partnership ("BookMyLube Canada"). This App is intended to provide you with information regarding products and services offered by BookMyLube Canada and its franchisees. By accessing, using, or downloading material from this App, you agree to the following terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="Agreements">The transactions you conduct through this App may be subject to written agreements between BookMyLube Canada and you. The information, products and services contained in this App do not change the terms of your written agreements with BookMyLube Canada. However, you agree to be bound by the transactions you conduct through this App. This App is intended for users who are 18 years old or older. \n \nThis App is intended solely for use in Canada. Activities involving certain countries may require compliance with various laws and regulations. Therefore, visitors to this App who are located in or affiliated with a country other than Canada should immediately exit this App. \n \nYou may receive a password to access certain areas of this App. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of the password, and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password. You agree to (a) immediately notify BookMyLube Canada of any unauthorized use of your password or any other breach of security, and (b) ensure that you fully log off from the App at the end of each session. This App does not require you to change your password; however, BookMyLube Canada encourages you to periodically change your password. BookMyLube Canada cannot and will not be liable for any loss or damage arising from your failure to comply with this section. \n \nBookMyLube Canada hereby grants to each user of this App a limited, revocable, non-transferable, and non-exclusive license to access this App on the terms and conditions contained herein. BookMyLube Canada reserves the right to limit or terminate any user`s access to this App, at any time, and without notice. Each user acknowledges and agrees having read and being bound by these terms of use for this App. Each user further acknowledges and agrees that BookMyLube Canada may, from time to time, revise and change these terms of use, without notice to user, and user shall be bound by any such changes and revisions, and it shall be user`s duty to be familiar with the then-current version of the terms of use. Each user also agrees to comply with any security procedures and policies that BookMyLube Canada may implement, from time to time, to protect BookMyLube Canada`s infrastructure. No user may allow a third party to access this App without the prior approval of BookMyLube Canada, and BookMyLube Canada may deny such approval in its sole discretion. BookMyLube Canada may also condition any access to this App on the user executing a written access agreement with BookMyLube Canada. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, each user is prohibited from allowing a third party to access this App with automated systems that extract data from this App. BookMyLube Canada reserves the right to charge fees for access to this App. Except as permitted by these terms of use or by BookMyLube Canada, no user shall post any content to this App. \n \nAll content on this App, including all the text, graphics, logos, designs, titles, button icons, photographs, graphs, sounds, data, images, audio and video clips available on this App ("Content"), and the compilation, collection, selection, arrangement, assembly and coordination of all Content is the property of BookMyLube Canada, its affiliates or its content suppliers, and is protected by Canadian and international copyright laws. All the Content may only be used by you in connection with your personal or business activities with BookMyLube Canada. You may make copies of selected portions of the Content, provided that such copies are made only for the purpose of your personal or business activities with BookMyLube Canada, and only if you maintain any proprietary notices contained in such Content. Any other use, including, but not limited to, the reproduction, modification, distribution, transmission, republication, display or performance of the Content for any other purposes, is strictly prohibited. \n \nTHIS APP AND THE PRODUCTS, SERVICES, PROMOTIONS AND PROGRAMS CONTAINED IN OR PROVIDED THROUGH THIS APP ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT ANY EXPRESS OR IMPLIED WARRANTY OF ANY KIND INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, NONINFRINGEMENT OF INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY, OR FITNESS FOR ANY PARTICULAR PURPOSE. IN NO EVENT SHALL BOOKMYLUBE CANADA OR ITS SUPPLIERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES WHATSOEVER (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, OR LOSS OF INFORMATION) ARISING OUT OF THE USE OF OR INABILITY TO USE THIS APP OR THE PRODUCTS, SERVICES, PROMOTIONS AND PROGRAMS CONTAINED IN OR PROVIDED THROUGH THIS APP, EVEN IF BOOKMYLUBE CANADA HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. THIS DISCLAIMER ALSO APPLIES TO YOUR USE OF ANY APP LINKED TO OR FROM THIS APP. IN ANY EVENT, BOOKMYLUBE CANADA SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY DAMAGES OR LOSSES OF ANY KIND IN AN AMOUNT GREATER THAN ONE HUNDRED ($100.00) CANADIAN DOLLARS. \n \nBookMyLube Canada in this App has attempted to be as accurate as possible, however, the information and materials contained in this App may not be current. BookMyLube Canada makes no representations or warranties as to the accuracy, reliability, or completeness of the information, text, graphics, links, or other items contained in this App or in any App linked to or from this App. BookMyLube Canada expressly disclaims liability for any errors or omissions in the information or materials contained in this App or in any App linked to or from the App, and also disclaim any duty to update the information or materials or to advise you when the information or materials are revised or discovered to be inaccurate, incomplete or erroneous. BookMyLube Canada may invalidate any transaction that is based on erroneous or inaccurate information supplied to this App by any person or BookMyLube Canada, its employees, contractors, or agents. \n \nThis App may include links to other Apps external to BookMyLube Canada’s Apps. These links are provided in order to help you quickly and easily find relevant information, services and/or products that may be of interest to you. It is your responsibility to decide whether any services and/or products available through any of these Apps are suitable for your purposes. Also, you may have linked to this App from an external App. We are not responsible for the owners or operators of any of these Apps, nor for any goods or services they supply, nor for the content of their Apps. Nothing contained in this App should be construed as an endorsement by BookMyLube Canada of any external App. We do not give or enter into any conditions, warranties or other terms or representations in relation to any of these Apps nor accept any liability in relation to any of these Apps (including, but not limited to, any liability arising out of any claim that the content of any external App infringes the intellectual property rights of any third party). \n \nBookMyLube Canada expressly disclaims any liability for any damage to your computer, information system, or other property due to your use of this App or your downloading any materials, text or images from this App, including, but not limited to, damage caused by viruses that may infect your computer or information system.</string>
    <string name="Trademarks">The trademarks, service marks, trade names, logos, and other indications of origin displayed in this App are owned by BookMyLube Canada or a third party who has granted BookMyLube Canada a right to use them. Nothing contained herein should be construed as granting any person or entity the right to use any such marks or names displayed here without the written permission of the owner. Other product and company names mentioned in this App may be trademarks or service marks of their respective owners. \n \nBookMyLube Canada does not wish to receive confidential or proprietary information from any user through its use of this App. If users of this App are (or are employed by) a competitor of BookMyLube Canada, users agree not to submit any competitively sensitive information, including, but not limited to, information with respect to the users` (or their employer`s) customer lists, supply, inventory, output, territories, markets, prices, and other sales arrangements for services and products that compete with services and products of BookMyLube Canada. Should any user of this App respond with information such as feedback data, questions, comments, suggestions, postings, or the like regarding this App or any products, services, promotions, programs or policies, such information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and will become the property of BookMyLube Canada, and BookMyLube Canada shall have no obligation of any kind with respect to such information and shall be free to reproduce, use, adapt, modify, create derivative works from, display, disclose, publish, broadcast, and distribute the information to others without any limitation or obligation whatsoever (including, but not limited to, the obligation to compensate user in any way). Users agree not to submit any material to this App that is illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or objectionable or that consists of or contains software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "spam." Users may not use a false email address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead BookMyLube Canada as to the origin of the material or other content. BookMyLube Canada reserves the right (but not the obligation) to remove or edit such content, but does not regularly review posted content. \n \nBookMyLube Canada reserves the right to make changes to this App and to any products, services, promotions, programs, or policies described in this App, and to suspend or terminate this App or the products, services, promotions, programs, or policies at any time, for any reason, and without notice. \n \nBookMyLube Canada may, from time to time, revise and modify these terms of use. Your continued access and use of this App bind you to any new terms or conditions. \n \nThe information at this site applies to Canada only and may not apply for other locations. Products of BookMyLube Canada, its affiliates, or its franchisees that are advertised on this site are not available outside of Canada or in all regions of Canada. Products are available according to local laws. All products are subject to the terms of applicable agreements. A reference to the price of a product does not mean it is an offer to sell. All products and prices may change without notice. All prices are in Canadian dollars. These terms and conditions are to be read with all other terms and conditions or disclaimers in this App. \n \nThese terms and conditions are governed by and are to be interpreted according to the law of the Province of British Columbia and the laws of Canada applicable therein. If there is a dispute about these terms and conditions, or any dispute about the App, whether in contract or tort, or otherwise, or you have any claim you wish to make against BookMyLube Canada respecting any matter arising, whether directly or indirectly, respecting use or existence of this App, then the British Columbia courts will have exclusive jurisdiction over the matter.</string>
    <string name="PrivacyPolicyStatement">BookMyLube Canada respects your privacy and takes great care in protecting your personal information. Please read our Privacy Policy below carefully so that you can understand how we may collect, use and disclose the personal information that you provide to us. \n \nBy accessing this App (including the BookMyLube Club page) you accept all the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. In particular, by submitting your personal data to us, you will be deemed to have given your permission for use and disclosure as referred to herein. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, you must immediately cease using and accessing this App and any content, services or products contained in or available from this App for which you need to provide personal information. \n \nFor each user of this App, BookMyLube Canada`s web server automatically recognizes the user`s domain name and email address (where possible). \n \nThis Privacy Policy covers our use and disclosure of your personal information (if any) that is collected through or in connection with this site, collected at the store while you are getting your vehicle serviced and collected through your enrollment and participation in the BookMyLube Club. For the purposes of this policy, "this site" means all the webpages related to the BookMyLube Canada App, including the BookMyLube Club page but excluding any links to third-party sites. \n \n You may be asked to voluntarily provide personal information (such as your name, address, telephone number and email address) when you are using this App, enrolling in the BookMyLube Club, using the BookMyLube Club services or getting your vehicle serviced at one of the BookMyLube locations in order to participate in contests, enroll in the BookMyLube Club, submit suggestions or comments, request information regarding becoming a franchisee or participate in other online interactive activities. You can choose not to provide certain requested personal information, but then you may not be able to use certain services provided by BookMyLube, participate in contests or the BookMyLube Club or access or use certain features of this App. \n \n BookMyLube Canada uses personal information (including name, address, telephone number and email) for the following purposes and as otherwise permitted by applicable law: \n \n\u2022  respond to queries or requests submitted by you \n \n\u2022  contact and correspond with you regarding your visits to BookMyLube locations \n \n\u2022  process orders or applications submitted by you \n \n\u2022  administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us \n \n\u2022  anticipate and resolve problems with any products or services supplied to you \n \n\u2022  create products or services that may meet your needs \n \n\u2022  conduct market research and tracking of sales data \n \n\u2022  inform you about our products and services, including contacting you by telephone or email \n \n\u2022  inform you of special BookMyLube Club members-only offers on our products and services \n \n\u2022  send you personalized service reminders prior to your next recommended visit \n \n\u2022  send you tips to help care for your car \n \n\u2022  inform you of community events \n \n\u2022  protect the security of this App when necessary \n \n\u2022  help us understand better visitors’ use of this App \n \n\u2022  fulfill prize. \n \nIn connection with BookMyLube Club, BookMyLube Canada will create a confidential profile for you, which will be used to provide services to you and facilitate your use of this App and services available to BookMyLube Club members only, and may keep a record of all communications with you. \n \nFrom time to time, BookMyLube Canada may send you email or other communications containing information about BookMyLube, current promotions or specials, this App and other matters BookMyLube Canada believes will interest you. Each email to you includes an unsubscribe feature and instructions on how to unsubscribe if you do not wish to receive future emails from BookMyLube Canada. You may also at any time ask BookMyLube Canada to stop sending you email, newsletters and other information by sending your request to directly at the co-ordinates noted below. Your request will be processed as soon as it is reasonably possible to do so. \n \nAs part of the services offered to you through our site, the information you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside of Canada. By way of example, this may happen if any of our servers or one of our service providers are from time to time located in a country outside of Canada. These countries may not have similar data protection laws to Canada. If we transfer your information outside of Canada in this way, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected. In addition, if you use our services while you are outside of Canada, your information may be transferred outside Canada in order to provide you with those services. \n \nBookMyLube Canada may use third parties (including affiliates, agents, suppliers and service providers) for the fulfillment of our obligations hereunder and to provide services to you. We require our affiliates, agents, suppliers and service providers to agree to use your personal information only for purposes for which it is provided to them, and to protect the privacy of your personal information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Except as set out in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose any personally identifiable information without your permission unless we are legally entitled or required to do so (for example, if required to do so by legal process or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime) or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and/or defend our rights, property or personal safety and those of our users/customers, etc. \n \nBookMyLube Canada may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the date and time you access this App, the type of internet browsers and the internet address you use, the App from which you linked to our site, the operating system you are using and the BookMyLube web pages read and images viewed. We may also aggregate details that you have submitted to the site (for example, your age and the town where you live). You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on this App. We may from time to time supply third parties with this non-personal or aggregated data for uses in connection with this site.</string>
    <string name="TheUseofCookies">We may store some information (commonly known as a cookie) on the device you used to view this App when you look at our site. We are able to read these cookies for information purposes when you revisit our App. The type of information we collect as a result of a cookie being accepted by you is specific to your device and includes the IP address, the date and time you visited the App, what parts of our App were looked at and whether the web pages requested were delivered successfully. This information is anonymous. \n \nYou can erase or block this information by changing the settings on your device. If you do erase or block this information you may not be able to utilize some features of this App. \n \nIf at any time this App offers any chat rooms, notice board facilities, newsgroups, etc, we may collect the information that you disclose. Such information will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Please note that we cannot be responsible for other parties use of the personal information that you make available to such third parties through any chat room, notice board, newsgroup, etc, on this site. Please be careful about the personal information you disclose in this way. \n \nIf at any time this site offers any e-mail, feedback or forum facilities, we may collect the information that you disclose. Such information will be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.</string>
    <string name="KeepingOurRecordsAccurate">We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details you have provided us, please contact our Privacy Officer.</string>
    <string name="SecurityofYourPersonalData">BookMyLube Canada has implemented technology and policies with the objective of protecting your privacy from unauthorized access and improper use and will update these measures as new technology becomes available, as appropriate. \n \nBookMyLube Canada has appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to minimize the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from members of BookMyLube Club and users through this App. Nevertheless, security risks cannot be eliminated and BookMyLube Canada cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be used or disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this policy.</string>
    <string name="OtherApps">We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other Apps even if you accessed the third-party App using links from our App or you linked to our App from a third-party App. \n \nWe recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact the owner or operator of that App if you have any concerns or questions.</string>
    <string name="PrivacyPolicy">BookMyLube Canada will respond to complaints from individuals or questions about our compliance with this policy and with applicable privacy laws. We will investigate and attempt to resolve all complaints. To challenge our compliance with this policy please contact directly at the co-ordinates listed below.\n \nIf you have any questions or concerns about your privacy and our role in protecting it, please contact our directly at the co-ordinates listed. \n \nbookmylube@gmail.com \n \nWe reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy at any time by posting a new Privacy Policy on this App.</string>

</resources>